I'm told the assassins
gave us useful information.
The rebels were trying to kidnap
you as a bargaining chip.
I see.
It sounds like they gave in rather easily.
It's possible they're lying.
You are clever, Noah.
But not to worry.
There is a way to find out if
one is speaking the truth.
It takes a thief to catch a thief.
I'm not knowledgeable
in the ways of torture,
so I'll just take his word for it.
Well done, Noah.
Had you been captured,
the empire would have been forced
to make a difficult choice.
Yes, sire.
Also, setting your sights on
their horses was brilliant.
I only just now gave the order
to buy up all the horse feed!
This has happened before,
but not this quickly.
Anyone could have had the idea
to use starvation tactics.
In fact, Albert had just
suggested starving the rebels
Albert Ararat
Crown Prince, Second Prince
to make examples of them.
But you realized that it could
cause them to attack our people
and chose to starve only their horses.
With your own funds, no less.
Your ideas...
and ability to act on them...
are most impressive, Noah.
That is not an easy thing to accomplish.
Thank you, sire.
I must reward you somehow.
I permit the addition of
a sword to Noah's crest.
The empire is a nation of warriors.
Adding a sword, the symbol of a warrior,
to one's crest without the emperor's
permission is sacrilege.
It may even be punished by death.
On the other hand, being granted the
emperor's permission to add one
is among the greatest
honors one can earn.
Cruz, issue the proclamation.
At once.
Thank you very much!
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
I have been waiting for you.
You're early.
There are only so many types of
feed designed to be transported,
and we know the route
used to bring it in.
It won't be difficult
to buy up all of it.
Also, regarding Karfun, the
leader of the rebels...
He is extremely tenacious and will do
whatever it takes to achieve his goal.
I'm certain it's nothing
you need to worry about,
but please, do be careful.
Why tell me this?
M-Master.
I apologize for interrupting.
There's a wounded man at the main gate
who says he has an urgent report.
It's an honor to meet you,
Your Imperial Highness.
I serve as a decurion in the
province of Adora in Almeria.
Yes.
A rebellion has begun in Almeria.
My superior started an uprising...
but I couldn't go along with it,
so I fled to report to you.
Episode 4
The Almerian Rebellion
So that's what the urgent report was?
Unfortunately for him,
the prince already knew of this.
Understood. Thank you for informing me.
Treat him.
Right away.
And give him a reward of five
hundred... no, a thousand rean.
Your Highness, what was that all about?
Hmm?
The information he brought isn't
even useful to you anymore.
That's true, but...
a mere decurion came here to
inform me, despite the danger.
I have to reward his loyalty.
That's why you promised
him so much money?
I believe he's worth it.
M... Master...
Enter.
Is something wrong?
You look pale.
Hey. What's wrong?
Th-This...
Money?
It looks to be around five hundred rean.
S-Someone I didn't know gave it to me...
a-as a reward for getting you...
to drink... this.
I was told... it's a sleeping drug.
You were to mix it into my drink,
then hand me over to them
once I fell asleep?
Yes, it seems so.
It's the rebels again.
Looks like they really want me.
I understand, but why did
you bring this to me?
I...
I could never betray you!
You helped my mother, after all...
and my village...
But they said I'd be killed if I didn't.
But still... I just
couldn't betray you...
So... um...
I understand.
What is this?
A reward.
They tried to buy your
betrayal for five hundred rean.
But you didn't do it,
so I'll add a zero to that.
F-Five thousand...
But... I can't accept this much!
Take it.
Thank you.
You are truly a generous master.
More importantly, there's
something I want you to do.
Of course! I'll do anything!
I'm going to drink this drug.
When I fall asleep, take me to them.
Master?
Then, I want you to run
and hide immediately.
They'll try to silence
you if you stick around.
M-Master...
What are you saying?
What a pain in the ass.
One stab with that creepy little
dagger, and it'd be all over.
That's supposed to be a
last resort, remember?
We can't go wrong if we
do what Karfun says.
They're my captors.
What's my situation?
Bound at the hands and feet, of course.
I was right to hide my weapon.
They would've taken it.
And they didn't take my ring.
My eyes have adjusted.
I thought I was in a room, but
this is the back of a wagon.
Show me your memories, Leviathan.
Hurry.
Tie him up good.
Hey, where'd the maid go?!
Leave her. We gotta get him out
before the guards catch on.
I see.
I understand the situation now.
Hey, which one of you
can't tie a knot?
What, you lookin' fer a fight?
Your big brother saved you last time,
but what's one li'l kid gonna—
What a waste of time.
I was hoping I'd get some useful
information, but you're just lackeys.
Y-You stupid little brat!
Get him!
Master!
What in the world is all this?
I-I'm very sorry.
I know you told me to hide,
but I was worried about you,
so... um...
You came to save me?
Y-Yes.
But... you did this by yourself?
Amazing...
Who's the captain here?
I am. It's an honor to meet
you, Thirteenth Prince.
Take care of them.
They're with the ones who
attacked me a few days ago.
Understood.
Don't touch that!
Step back.
O-Of course...
Master?
Is this the dagger they
were talking about?
So much malice...
Through Leviathan,
I can sense a curse on it, too.
Sorcery...
It's filled with the hatred
of the one who cursed it.
Could this be...?
Can you do this?
It should be easy for a
water magic sword like you, right?
Then show me.
Ah, you're here.
Excellent, Noah. Well done.
Last night, the leader of the rebels
was pierced through the brow
by a pillar of water that
appeared out of nowhere.
It was your doing, was it not?
You had your magic sword do it.
Yes.
As always, word travels fast.
I used the hatred in the
dagger to guide Leviathan
to the rebel leader with
a long-distance sniping shot.
It seems like it worked.
After that, the Almerian rebels,
having lost their leader,
were quickly suppressed
by Fourth Prince Henry.
Nearly all those involved in plotting
the uprising have been arrested.
Your Majesty's judgment is requested
in deciding their punishment.
Ready the horses and cattle.
Every last one of them will be
drawn and quartered!
Brilliant!
Excellent judgment!
Just wait, Noah.
They will pay at once for the crime of
launching a rebellion in your fief!
If I may, Your Majesty...
You mustn't do that.
What?!
What is the meaning of this, Noah?
They must be punished in
accordance with the law.
According to imperial law, rebel leaders
are to be cut in half at the waist,
third-degree supporters and
accomplices are to be hanged,
and any others are to be
beheaded for participating.
Even if "drawn and quartered"
is simply idiomatic,
no such punishment exists
in the laws of this empire.
But these people sullied your name!
If the emperor takes the
initiative in breaking the law,
it can throw his supremacy into disarray.
Please reconsider.
Hmph. Your logic is sound.
You've done well to
catch me in my mistake.
But a tame punishment
will not satisfy me.
Punish them to the fullest
extent of the law!
There will be no commutations!
Will that suffice?
I see no problems whatsoever.
First Prime Minister.
Sire?
I assume you heard all that.
Noizhill
First Prime Minister
I'll let you handle this.
Understood.
Th-That's the Thirteenth Prince for you!
How brave of him to admonish
the emperor like that!
And without the slightest
change in his expression!
His genius is truly a
gift from the heavens!
A child prodigy indeed!
Remarkable!
His conviction is strong!
You stopped me from sullying this
empire's good name in history.
I must reward you.
Yes. I shall grant you a title.
Any of my children may be capable
of simply admonishing me,
but to do so rightly
is a valuable talent.
To make your cleverness
known to all my subjects...
I grant you the title "Wise"!
MP: F
Water: E+S
Strength: F+F
Wind: F
Stamina: F+F
Earth: F
Intelligence: F+F
Light: F
Spirit: F+F
Dark: F
Speed: F
Dexterity: F+F
The prince has a new title!
Thirteenth Imperial Prince
This has never happened before!
Wise Prince
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Noah, if only you had been
born a bit earlier...
Long live the Wise Prince!
Long live Wise Prince Noah!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
By the way, Noah, the knight
selection exam is soon.
Have you decided how you will judge it?
I have a plan. May I show you after this?
Yes.
Go ahead.
I will have the participants
attack me in this way
and judge them based on how
close their attacks get to me.
Brilliant, as usual.
This reduces the burden on you and
eases the judgment process.
But it is not without its risks.
If any contender is powerful enough
to break through your defenses...
I am prepared to deal with that.
Well said.
That is what makes you my son,
an imperial prince...
no, the Wise Prince!
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Still...
do you not think saying,
"if only you had been born earlier"
before the public was a bit much?
And what is the issue?
Not only did he admonish me,
but he took out an enemy leader without
even going to the battlefield.
It's unprecedented!
Besides...
that magic sword of his really does
seem to possess terrifying power.
Yes.
Cruz.
Sire.
Bring it out.
Yes, sire.
The legends say that the true seal
on Leviathan must not be broken.
But perhaps, if Noah were to do it...
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu